Guide to the Albert Ellis papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Audio Visual Material, 1953-2007
  - Subseries V.1: Audio cassettes, 1966-2007
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 195)
      (RET Dem, Woman nt helpg her child in kindergarten; RET Dems, Urbana, 1981 October 1, AJSOL, Nd to hv children)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 195)
      (RET Dems, Dayton, 1982 July 21; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 195)
      (RET Dem, 1. Male puttg self down, 1979 January 22, 2. Woman lonely; RET Dem, San Diego, 1981 October 22, 1. Man self downg abt relatg)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 195)
      (RET Dems, Philly, 1983 February; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 195)
      (RET Dem, Woman Deprsd Abt Borg Job, Greenwich, Conn.,1981 October )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 195)
      (RET Dems, Irvine, 1981 October 23, 4A; RET Dems, Irvine, 1981 October 23, 4B)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 195)
      (RET Dems, Dallas, 1983 June; RET Dems, Lubbock, 1983June )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 195)
      (RET Demonstrations, 1. Male w. fear of failing, 2. Woman who has to be recognized, AGPA, St. Louis, 1981 April; RET Demonstration, Male who gets short tempered, AGPA, St. Louis, 1981 April )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 195)
      (RET Dems, Montgomery & Dallas, 1983 June; RET Dems, Montgomery,1983 June )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 195)
      (RET Dems, Baltimore, 1981 November; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 195)
      (Sex Therapy, AASEC, 1976 July, FL)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 195)
      (RET Dems, India, 1980 July, 1. Male deprsd abt depresn; RET Dem, Jerusalem, 1980 July 13, Male w. thin body)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 195)
      (RET Dem, Lugano, Woman whose coworkers r. dependent on her; RET Dems, Lugano, 1980 August )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 195)
      (RET Dem, L.A., 1980 February, 1. Woman w. poor analytic therapy, 2.; RET Dems, Bombay, 1980 July )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 195)
      (RET Dems, Riverside, 1981 October 24; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 195)
      (RET Dem, 1981)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 195)
      (RET Dems, Bombay, 1980 July, 1. Male self consci abt walkg; RET Dems, Bombay, 1980 July )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 195)
      (RET Dems, Seattle, 1981 December, Gunnars, Angry at Wife; Evalyn continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems Vancouver, 1981 October 26, C90; RET Dems, Des Moines, November 21)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dem., Psychiatrist Anx abt pub spkg, Jerusalem, 1980 July 13; RET Dem, 1980 April 20, Boston, Male horrified by cunnilinctus)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dem, Detroit, 1979 June, 1. Woman afrd of criticism, 2. Ed: Unassertv w. woman he is afraid to hurt; Woman jealous of H’s ogling other women, RET Dem, Detroit, 1979 June )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems, Anchorage,1979 July; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dem, Janet Wolfe & A. Ellis w. woman who is self downg abt physical handicap, Barbara, 1979 April; RET Dems, NYC, 1979 April 8, Janet Wolfe w. woman who wants career & relationship)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dem, Schiz woman angry at F, M, & ex-therapist, Carbondale, 1979 May; RET Dems, Boston, 1979 May, 1. Roseanne)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems, Philadelphia, 1980 October 5; RET Dems, Rutgers, 1980 October 4)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dem, LA,1979 October; RET Dem, Women worrying abt gtg & kpg a job, LA, 1979 October )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET, Amer Psychiatric Assn, 1978 May, Dr. Albert Ellis; Dr. Albert Ellis, continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems., Chicago; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems, Denver, 1978 March; continued, RET Dems, Denver,1980 March)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems, Toronto, 1980 Ocotber 26; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems, 1980 July 9, N.Y.C.; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (A, RET Dems, St. Louis, 1980 September 24, Woman glty abt nt hvg a child; B, continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems, Sault Ste Marie, 1980 October 25; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems, NYC, 1979 November 9; RET Dem, NYC, 1979 November )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems, NYC, 1979 September 3, Bob Harper w. Procrastination; RET Dem, NYC 1979 September 3, A Ellis, Rabbi falsely usg title)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dem, 1978 April, Atlanta, Ashmed of being "illegitimate"; RET Dem, Albany, 1976 April 29, Woman upset abt H’s illegit child)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dem, 1. Towson, 1979 March, Male who is afraid he will teach RET prly, 2.; RET Dem., Boston, 1979 May, 1., 2. Female afrd of pub apreance)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems, Nicholls State, La, 1979 February; RET Dems, Woman glty & angry w her D, 1979 February)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems, 1978 November, Sacramento, 1. Woman angry at H. & self-downing, 2. Sacramento: Woman afrd of any rejection)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems, 1980 October 12, NYC; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems, 1979 April; RET Dems)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems w. Susan Leblen, NYC, 1980 April 13, 1. Elaine, Indecsv abt relaship; 2. Done mainly by Susan, 3. Done mainly by Susan, Murray--Prob. of impotence)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dem., Woman who can’t show affection, 1979 October; RET Dem, Biloxi, 1979 October, Woman angry at dead son)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dem, 1980 August, Birmingham; RET Dem, NYC, 1980 October 12)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dem, Colo Springs, 1980 August, Christian female afrd to get trapd in Mrj; RET Dems, Colo Spgs, 1980 August )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems, Montreal, 1980 August; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dem, Austin, 1980 May; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Seattle; RET Portland)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems., Seattle, 1980 May; RET Dems., Portland, 1980 May )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dem, Towson, Md, 1978 March 11, Woman Anx about askg for raise; RET Dem, Atlanta, 1978 April, Male has trble tlkg to clients abt money)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET, 1979 February, Athens; continued, RET Athens, O., 1979 February)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems, Athens,1979 February; RET Dems, Ohio Wesleyan)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dem, Olympia, 1978 June; RET Dems, 1978 June, #2)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dem, 1977 April )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Workshop, University of Missouri at Kansas City, 1978 April; continued, RET Dem, partial)(Handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No permission)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems, Towson, 1979 March; RET Dems, Towson, 1979 March)Handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No permission)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems, Stony Brook, 1979 March 10; RET Dems, Stony Brook, 1979 March 10)(Handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No permission)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (February 29, RET Dems, Houston, Woman glty abt hvg a lover; RET Dem, Overwt woman, Dalphna, Houston, February 29)(Handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No permission)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (RET Dems, 1979 February, Houston; RET Dems)(Handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No permission)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1989 November 25, 1. Man who is bisexual & married, 2. Woman in love with a married man)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1997 September 12, 1. Woman angry at her mother, 2. Man horrified at noises connected w his alc. Father)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1988 September 30, 1. 28 yr old male nt succeedg w. women, 2. 20 yr old woman who must have perfect marks; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1987 January 16, 1. Rosella, Hates small talk but needs people’s approval, 2. Woman who wnts better design job without takg a pay cut)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1987 August 29, 1. Woman who hates to move to NY to continue her relationship, 2. Man who hates commuting to England for his psychological work)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1987 October, 1. Man under work stress, 2. Man acting shittily to mate; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. workshop, 1992 July 24, 1. Woman w. angry daughters, 2. Woman depressed about summer)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 April 12, 1. Male who overspends, 2. Woman angry at coworker)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1994 April 8, 1. Young woman who is perfectionistic, 2. Partial)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1992 August 14, 1. Jim--anx after being mugged, 2. Woman stl angry at her parents despit Disputg)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1993 June 17, 1. Woman w. fat daughter, 2. Woman angry at men who disappoint her)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 August 9, 1. Woman harassed at work, 2. Woman procrastinating)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1993 September 24, 1. Male, anx & deprsd, 2. Male anx abt job interviews)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 March 10, 1. Robin: Fear of rejection by Men, 2. Dan: Social worker with nasty psychiatrist coworker; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Night Workshop, 2000 July 3, 1. ORP woman, 2. woman w. thoughts abt other men that her husband)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (1999 August 13, 1. Woman deprsd abt designg voca, 2. Man panickd abt panic)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (1996 November 22, Fri Workshop, 1. Woman a failure bks husband divorced her)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1997 July 17, 1. Man who procrastinates on sci. papers, 2. Student hostile to authority)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1998 May 14, 1. Male who is being rejected for dates, 2. Woman who has LFT abt getting a degree)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1991 January 11, 1. Woman angry at husband’s ex-wife, 2. Man downg self for doing poorly at prep course)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1986 January 24, 1. Russell, Angry at others & self for actg badly, 2. John, gtg up late & LFT)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 July 27, 1. Woman put down by her fmly, 2. Man not contributg to the world)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 January 18, 1. Lucy: Woman who rat packs, 2. Man who downs himself abt job & failing in marriage)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1985 December 6, 1. Susie, Afraid to be close to people, 2. Female unable to be alone)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 2000 January 21, 1. Man who fails at art, 2. Man who has very difficult coworkers)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1999 November 19, 1. Woman angry at her mother, 2. Woman who can’t decide between 2 careers)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (1997 April 25, Fri Workshop, 1. Katie, Father very hostile, 2. Anne Marie, Mother belittles her & Fathers family)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1992 September 21, 1. Male who hs to fight w. people on erued, 2. Woman who gets hurt when men leave her)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1994 November 11, 1. Woman w. mental deficient child, 2. Man who can’t get enuf sex)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1984 September 13, 1. Man whose W. spends too much, 2. Woman who cant meet suitable males)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1992 March 6, 1. Joyce, Woman hates living in NJ, 2. Susan, won’t kp sayg No to male friend)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 June 28, 1. Woman guilty abt not being close to her family, 2. Man glty abt his dead father)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1985 June 14, 1. Older woman deprsd after accident, 2. Man who May be evicted from cheap apt; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Night Workshop, 1985 July 12, 1. Woman hung upon wrong man, 2. TAMJO, Woman stymied politically & in her org.; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1985 July 5, 1. Woman whose lover was cheap, 2. Male who cnt find suitable friends & lvers; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1. HCSAR, Male angry at Brother, 1985 November 29, 2. Male angry at supervisor; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1986 March 21, 1. Julia--Stays w. abuseive men too long, 2. Lisa--"abnormal" for nt needg to be maried; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1992 April 8, 1. Yng woman who md important errors, 2. Man who is being harmed by marriage counseling)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1991 March 1, 1. Man addicted to fatty foods, 2. Man addicted to stress & alc, with Lydia)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1991 February 1, 1. Tracy--Young woman who fears rejectn, 2. Rita--Woman whose mother doesn’t call her)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Nite Workshop, 1986 February 20, 1. Young woman whose family opposes her mrj to non-Jewish male, 2. Male who cnt lose weight)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1992 May 22, 1. Man who nds certnty, 2. Man who isn’t too gd at paintg)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1993 November 19, 1. Woman raped, 2. Man angry)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1988 March 18, 1. Law student who must do better at law, 2. Unmotivated male who is not actively datg; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1986 February 28, 1. Male w. achg gums & teeth, 2. Leon--Male rejected by female; continued
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1985 November 22, 1. Hilda--Dire lv nd [Resistant], 2. Susan--Abysmal LFT abt little hassles; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1985 August 16, 1. Overwt woman afrd to mt men & to write, 2. Woman, nurse, burnd out w. head nurse job; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, >1992 June 12, 1. Herb--sad he move to Miami, Sylvia--procrastinatn)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1993 April 9, 1. Employer angry at his employee, 2. Woman who cnt stop smokg)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1985 December 13, 1. Retired woman who shld be mr involved, 2. Young woman who has to be in control; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 December 20, 1. Man angry at coworkers & self downing, only partly recorded)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1999 August 6, 1. Mentally ill W. angry at M. Who stole from her, 2. Young Male angry at his parents for ignoring him)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1999 August 27, 1. Woman angry at Da for not raisg her child well, 2. Woman angry at alcoholic father & brother)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1981 May 1)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1985 October 5, 1. Alc. cnselor who’s supervisor is unprofessional & bigoted, 2. Woman who is too nurturg to men)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1985 October 26, 1. Herb--Nt doing dietg crse)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1. Jerry--Angry at mechanic, 2. Dan--Accomplishg but losing pleasure in life)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (1985 February 22, Friday Workshop; 1. Man procrastinatg on Demos, 2. Woman w. Injury)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Wkshop, 1990 September 28, 1. Shl this woman return to Eng, 2. Man who nds the best possible career)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Side 1, Fri Nite Workshop, 1981 June 26; Fri Nite Workshop, 1981 June 26, Dr. Ellis, Side 2)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1992 June 27, 1. Male lonely & deprsd, 2. Dan, angry & deprsd abt friend’s behvr)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 196)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1985 July 26, 1. Debbie--Perf. Anxiety, 2. Woman who May be infertile; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 June 21, 1. Man who is afraid to be assertive, 2. Woman who is a failure as an actress)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 May 31, 1. Woman eatg extra fd, 2/Male ostracized by religious group)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 July 19, 1. Woman afraid of rejection, 2. Woman with lack discipline)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1993 November 26, 1. Male who nds gd sex w. ex-wf, 2. Woman addicted to her 2 cats)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1991 April 17, 1. Rose--afrd to talk to men, 2. with Jean Linscott, Yng Male--upset abt rejectn by woman)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1986 January 3, 1. Young man debatg abt changing grad school, see other side; Fri Workshop, 1986 January 3, 1. see other side, 2. Young woman going w. married man--Lisa)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1992 February 21, 1. Woman w. bird phobia, 2. Man afrd of rejection, Dr. Ellis)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 August 31, 1. Male w. Peyronies sex problem, 2. Female who is unenergetic; Fri. Workshop,1990 August 30, 1. Male w. Peyronies sex prob., 2. Female who is unenergetic)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 January 27, 1. Woman afrd of commitment, 2. Woman askg for job guarantee)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Nite Workshop, 1994 July, 1. Stephanie, deprsd abt losg job, 2. Kelly--low self-esteem)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1994 October 28, 1. Karin, Angry at black man who didn’t listen to her, 2. Woman anx abt her anx, with Mark Jergesen)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, (Low audio), 1995 February 24, 1. Woman whose H. won’t wrk, 2. Woman w. poor body image)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1994 October 22, 1. Woman who peple & not heedg, 2. Woman w. frightening nightmares)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Nite Workshop, 1981 June 4)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1974 August 9, 1. Won’t ask for loans back, 2. Woman whose sister is neg)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1999 April 9, 1. Mother who must help her daughter, 2. Woman who won’t assert herself w. her husband & mother)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 October 12, 1. Woman who dislikes job & cn’t decide on a new career, 2. Woman rejected by her lver)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1985 August 9, 1. Man who can’t commit self to one kind of work, 2. Woman whose brother supposedly robbed her; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 November 5, 1. Woman whose husband abuses her; 2. Paranoid Male)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1999 July 16, 1. Man who can’t stop smokg, 2. Woman whose friend is on coke)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1985 September 6, 1. Jack--Shall he quit therapist, 2. Young female--shall she try for disability)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1992 March 28, 1. Male who procrastinates, 2. Woman angry)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, AE, 1. Teacher who wants more adventurous job, 2. Female researcher in doubt about who to work with)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1994 September 23, 1. June --Psychotic, 2. Unassertv woman, 3. Overweight male)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1994 July 1, 1. Man who wnts to avoid operation for cancer, 2. Woman who is angry at roommate & her friend)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 2000 March 4, 1. Very depressed woman, 2. Man whose fiance rejected him)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 June 14, 1. Woman angry abt falling on ice, 2. Woman who lost her lver being overwt)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1987 June 12, 1. Man with panic about panic in elevators, 2. David--Stutterer ashamed of talking slowly; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1987 August 14, 1. Woman lonely after giving up male friend, 2. Man afraid to mk career decision; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1987 October 9, 1. Woman depressed after breaking off relationship, 2. Chinese male student depressed about loss of woman friend & studying poorly)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1987 November 20, 1. Woman who is shy in groups, 2. Woman whose Mother & Brother are seriously ill, is divorcing & has 2 sons leaving; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1. Severely depressed woman, 2. Gay performer afraid to be too honest in his performances.; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1986 August 1, 1. Mother who puts 11pm curfew on her 18yr old Da, 2. Woman who’s lover keeps talking about his ex-lover)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1987 May 29, 1. Woman with insomnia, 2. Woman who won’t let people ride in her car)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1997 December 12, 1. Woman not doing anythg abt employment, 2. Man angry at ex-wife’s criticism)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 November 17, 1. Young male afrd to tlk to females, 2. Young male afraid he won’t get A’s in school)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1998 Ocotber 30, 1. Man afraid of failg in cnselg business, 2. Man afraid to fail as a counselor)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 2000 August 4, 1. Woman w. obnoxious daughter, 2. Jim--overeatg male)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 2000 June 23, 1. Woman with "fear of success", 2. Woman fearful of loving)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (2000 August 25, Fri Workshop, 1. Woman who is perfectionistic, 2. Woman who sleeps little & worries)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 July 13, 1. Male angry at his woman friend; continued, 2. Father angry at his son)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1991 February 8, 1. Julia--Angry at son, 2. Ron--Angry abt the war)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 August 18, 1. Woman havg trble with a shnooky male, 2. Woman savg useless thgs in her apartment)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1999 September 3, 1. Man who is afrd of being trapped in a relationship, 2. Woman downg herself for stayg too long in a relationship)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1997 September 19, 1. Man who nds certainty, 2. Woman whose lover is glty abt hvg sex)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1994 April 1, 1. Man angry at his young son, 2. Woman whose man friend doesn’t communicate)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 2000 June 16, Woman who is paranoid abt having sex w. a man)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1999 January 22, 1. Woman anx abt her husband’s anx, 2. Woman not dietg & exercising)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1999 March 12, 1. Woman afraid she will become schizophrenic, 2. Man neglecting his family members)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 197)